(Officiant) Now the groom Jun-mo Park and the bride Yu-jeong Yoo
（司仪）现在新郎朴俊模和 新娘柳有正
In the presence of relatives and friends
在亲戚朋友面前
May we become a couple who will share joys and sorrows throughout our lives.
愿我们成为一生同甘共苦的情侣。
I made a firm oath [calm music]
我立下坚定的誓言 [平静的音乐]
Accordingly, the officiant confirmed that this marriage was amicable.
据此，主婚人确认这桩婚姻 是友好的。
I solemnly declare before you
我在你面前郑重声明
[Jae-man yells]
[杰曼大喊]
[Guests are making noise]
[客人发出噪音]
(Jae-man) Give me money, you bastard!
（Jae-man）给我钱，你这个混蛋！
My money, give me my money! [Sound of employee trying to stop him]
我的钱，给我钱！ [员工试图阻止他的声音]
(Junmo) Hey, really, what’s wrong?
（俊模）嘿，真的，怎么了？
Why, why, why, huh? [Jae-man sobs]
为什么，为什么，为什么，嗯？ [Jae-man抽泣]
(Jaeman) A good day like today
（Jaeman）像今天这样的美好一天
Abby should get some!
艾比应该买一些！
(Junmo) Mr... [Jae-man’s heavy breathing]
（俊模）先生…… [Jae-man沉重的呼吸声]
Come on, take this.
来吧，拿着这个。
- (Junmo) Go quickly - (Jaeman) Ha, this bastard is this
- (Junmo) 快点 - (Jaeman) 哈，这个混蛋就是这个
Are you kidding me?
你在开玩笑吧？
(Jae-man) Hey, I’m the bastard!
(Jae-man) 嘿，我是混蛋！
Do you think you came here to buy jjjuba , you asshole?
你以为你来这里是为了买jjjuba吗 ，你这个混蛋？
Give me some more
再给我一些
[Jae-man cheers] (Jun-mo) Pick it up and go quickly
[Jae-man 欢呼] (Jun-mo) 拿起它，快点走
- (Junmo) Please go, please! - (Jae-man) Thank you!
- （俊模）请走吧，拜托！ -（在万）谢谢！
[Jae-man’s surprised voice]
[在万惊讶的声音]
(Jaeman) My daughter-in-law is pretty!
(Jaeman) 我的儿媳妇很漂亮！
[Jaeman laughs]
[杰曼大笑]
[Guests are making noise]
[客人发出噪音]
Ha, Mr.
呵呵，先生。
[sigh]
[叹]
[Car acceleration sound]
[汽车加速声音]
[Fighting sounds]
[打斗声]
[Gunshot sound] [Groaning of member 1]
[枪声] [成员1的呻吟声]
[Groaning from member 2]
[成员2的呻吟]
[Groaning from member 3]
[成员3的呻吟]
[gunshot sound]
[枪声]
(Yongdae) Fuck you!
（龙大）操你妈的！
[Ongdae cheers]
[翁大欢呼]
[clunking sound]
[叮当声]
[Ambient sound fading] [Hearing breathing]
[环境声音减弱] [听到呼吸声]
[Organization member 4’s scream]
[组织4号成员的尖叫声]
[Ambient sounds becoming clearer] [Sounds of fighting]
[周围的声音变得更加清晰] [战斗的声音]
[Groaning from member 5]
[成员5的呻吟]
(Organization Member 6) Oh, fuck!
（组织成员6）哦，操！
[Groaning from member 6]
【6号成员的呻吟】
[Uijeong’s encouraging sound]
[义正鼓励的声音]
[Heavy breathing]
[沉重的呼吸]
[The doctor's heavy breathing]
【医生粗重的呼吸声】
[dark music]
[黑暗音乐]
[Heavy breathing]
[沉重的呼吸]
[Groans of organization members]
【组织成员的呻吟声】
[Uijeong’s encouraging sound]
[义正鼓励的声音]
[Groaning from member 7]
[7号成员的呻吟]
[Justice's groan]
[正义的呻吟]
[shout]
[喊]
[The spirit of organization member 8]
【组织成员精神8】
[Groaning of organization member 8]
【组织成员8的呻吟】
[sudden sound]
[突然的声音]
[Sound of pulling out mugwort] [Organization member 9 screams]
[拔艾草的声音] [组织成员9尖叫]
[Groaning from 10 members of the organization]
【组织10名成员的呻吟】
[Groaning of organization member 11]
【组织成员11的呻吟】
[Groans of organization members]
【组织成员的呻吟声】
[Groans from organization member 12]
【组织成员12的呻吟声】
[Junmo’s heavy breathing]
[君莫粗重的呼吸声]
[Groaning from member 13]
[13号成员的呻吟]
[Rough breathing]
[粗重的呼吸]
[Groaning of organization member 14]
【组织成员14的呻吟】
[Scream of organization member 15]
[组织成员15的尖叫声]
[The doctor's surprised gasp]
[医生惊讶的喘息声]
[Junmo’s moans]
[俊模的呻吟声]
[Scream of justice] [Groaning of organization member 16]
【正义的呐喊】 【组织成员16的呻吟】
(준모) 일로 와, 이 개새끼야
(준모) 일로 와, 개새끼야
[Gi-cheol yells]
[基哲喊道]
[Uijeong’s heavy breathing]
[义正粗重的呼吸声]
[Rough breathing]
[粗重的呼吸]
[Screaming sound] [Screams of gang members]
[尖叫声] [帮派成员的尖叫声]
[dark music]
[黑暗音乐]
(Junmo) Ha, Mr.
(Junmo) Ha, Mr.
Mr. Lee…
李先生…
[Interesting music]
[有趣的音乐]
(Haeryun) Ugh, it must be hard to clean.
（海云）哎呀，一定很难清理吧。
[Rough breathing]
[粗重的呼吸]
To this extent
到这个程度
Why do you do it?
你为什么要这么做？
Just what
只是什么
There's someone I want to protect
有一个我想保护的人
[snort]
[哼哼]
This is the first time I disobeyed my father.
这是我第一次违背父亲的话。
Boss Jeong
郑老板
Prove it to me
证明给我看
That I wasn't wrong
说明我没有错
When will the good news come?
好消息什么时候传来？
Sorry, not yet…
抱歉，还没有…
(Jockey) Let’s wait a little longer.
（骑师）我们再等一会儿吧。
These idiots even gave me medicine.
这些白痴 还给我吃药。
[nervous music]
[紧张的音乐]
(Jongryeol) Mr.
（金钟烈）先生
[Groaning of organization member 17]
【组织成员17的呻吟】
(Jongryeol) Come out, Mr. Lee…
(金钟烈) 出来吧，李先生……
- (Organization Member 18) What is it? - (Organization Member 19) What kind of bastard…
-（组织成员18）这是什么？ ——（组织成员19）什么混蛋……
What are you talking about, you fucking bastard?
你在说什么啊， 你这个混蛋？
(Jockey) Don’t be afraid… [Jockey's groan]
（骑师）别害怕…… [骑师的呻吟]
Hey, you fucking bastard!
嘿，你这个该死的混蛋！
(Heesung) If you don’t want to be left behind, stay still.
（熙成）如果你不想落后， 就保持安静。
(Jockey) Are these guys crazy?
（骑师）这些家伙疯了吗？
[Jockey's groan]
[骑师的呻吟声]
- (Heeseong) Stay still, you bastard - (Jockey) Hey, you bastard!
- (Heeseong) 别动，你这个混蛋 - (骑师) 嘿，你这个混蛋！
(Jockey) I know who I am!
（骑师）我知道我是谁！
[Jockey's groan]
[骑师的呻吟声]
[scream]
[尖叫]
[dark music]
[黑暗音乐]
[Jockey's groan]
[骑师的呻吟声]
Please tell Kanemoto clearly.
请清楚地告诉金本。
Come to Korea, look me in the eye and apologize.
来韩国吧， 看着我的眼睛道歉。
There are no items until then.
在那之前没有任何项目。
"reconstruction"
“重建”
[Sound of putting it down]
[放下的声音]
(Shape) In preparation for an unexpected situation
（形状）为意外情况做准备
Our team members are standing by
我们的团队成员随时待命
Let’s start with treatment.
我们先从治疗开始吧。
[heavy music]
[重音乐]
[moaning]
[呻吟]
[Heeseong and Gicheol sigh]
[熙成和基哲叹息]
[Calm music]
[平静的音乐]
(Junmo) Mr. Uijeong, tomorrow
(Junmo) 义正先生，明天
I was assigned to Seoul.
我被分配到首尔。
It's flying...
它正在飞...
Well, it would be nice to go to Seoul, really.
嗯， 去首尔真是太好了。
that…
那…
There must be a lot of good guys too
一定也有很多好人
Well, I guess it would be nice, but
嗯，我想这会很好，但是
Don't meet those bastards
别遇见那些混蛋
Just, well…
只是，好吧……
Come with me...
跟我来...
Do you want to meet?
你想见面？
So now
所以现在
What I mean is, that…
我的意思是，那……
a little with me
和我在一起一点
long time
很久
see you
再见
[shaking breathing]
[呼吸颤抖]
[Calm music]
[平静的音乐]
No, it’s not that expensive. [Uijeong’s light smile]
不，没那么贵。 [义正淡淡的微笑]
(Jun’s mother) No, Geun, I’m at work…
（Jun的妈妈）不，Geun，我在工作......
[Takes a deep breath]
[深吸一口气]
[Rough breathing]
[粗重的呼吸]
(Kichul) Oh
（基楚尔）哦
Boss, I need a change of clothes.
老板，我需要换衣服。
You had a hard time, kids?
孩子们，你们过得很辛苦吗？
We are mainly treating those in critical condition.
我们主要治疗病情危重的人。
Keep monitoring the situation and contact me immediately if anything happens.
持续关注事态发展， 如有任何情况请立即联系我。
(Accountant) Yes
(会计师) 是
[Gicheol sighs]
[吉哲叹息]
(Kichul) Are you okay?
（基楚尔）你还好吗？
Boss, are you okay?
老板，你还好吗？
Aren’t you hungry?
你不饿吗？
I'm sorry
对不起
Do you want to go eat?
你想去吃饭吗？
[cell phone operation sound]
【手机操作声】
[Call connection tone]
[呼叫连接音]
[Out of office sound]
[外出声音]
[cell phone operation sound]
【手机操作声】
[cell phone ringing sound]
[手机铃声]
[Voice guidance] This is the first message.
[语音指导] 这是第一条消息。
(Kichul) I’m Kicheol
(基哲) 我是基哲
today's day
今天
It may be very difficult, but I hope you can endure it.
这可能会很困难，但 我希望你能忍受。
[heavy music]
[重音乐]
I will make sure nothing dangerous like this happens again in the future.
我会确保以后不再发生类似的危险事件。
I'm so sorry
我很抱歉
[Call end sound]
[通话结束声音]
[cell phone operation sound]
【手机操作声】
[Voice guidance] Next message
[语音指导] 下一条消息
(Junmo) Uijeong, it’s me.
(俊模) 义正，是我。
are you okay?
你还好吗？
Were you very surprised?
你是否感到非常惊讶？
Today's work
今天的工作
I couldn't help it either
我也忍不住了
our investigation
我们的调查
It's a dangerous investigation that requires risking one's life.
这是一项危险的调查，需要冒着生命危险。
So please
所以，请
I'm asking you to stay out of this case.
我请求你不要介入这起案件。
Uijeong, I really can’t stop.
义正，我真的停不下来了。
[Junmo’s sigh]
[君莫的叹息]
So, I will quickly conclude the investigation.
所以，我 会尽快结束调查。
Then I'll go back again
然后我会再回去
sorry
对不起
[cell phone operation sound]
【手机操作声】
[Doorbell sounds]
[门铃响]
(Kichul) He’s our employee.
（Kichul）他是我们的员工。
Well, I couldn’t eat dinner.
好吧，我晚饭吃不下了。
Uh, yeah
呃，是的
Come in, come in
进来吧进来吧
yes
是的
(Kichul) Come in
(基楚尔) 进来吧
[Jongryeol’s sigh]
[金钟烈的叹息]
Now we have eaten all of Seoul under the Han River.
现在我们已经吃遍了汉江下的整个首尔。
[sigh]
[叹]
we?
我们？
go in first
先进去
Let's see each other for a few days
我们几天见一次面吧
[Japanese] Should a father apologize to his child?
[日语] 父亲应该 向孩子道歉吗？
You're bold
你真大胆
(Nishigawa) What are you going to say to Oyabun?
（西川） 你想对亲文说什么？
[Sound of putting it down]
[放下的声音]
(Gi-cheol) [Korean] China plans to double the volume
(Gi-cheol) [韩语] 中国 计划将产量翻倍
Why did you accept it?
你为什么接受它？
During the last transaction, we were unable to process the quantity due to a mistake on our part.
在上次交易中， 由于我们的失误，我们无法处理该数量。
I heard there is a lot of stock left .
听说还有很多存货。
[Junmo’s sigh]
[君莫的叹息]
(Junmo) This time we have to accept that amount.
（纯模）这次我们 必须接受这个金额。
Won't broken trust be restored?
破碎的信任不会 恢复吗？
But the volume has increased so much that I have to process it all.
但数量增加太多 ，我必须全部处理。
It wouldn't be easy if it weren't for Japan.
如果不是日本，这一切都不容易。
president
总统
Aren't you speaking too strongly to Japan ?
你对日本说话是不是太强硬了？
All this time, I called Kanemoto my father.
一直以来，我都称金本为 父亲。
[sigh]
[叹]
(Kichul) But because of that bastard, not only us
（Kichul）但是因为那个混蛋， 不仅仅是我们
Even Uijeong’s older sister almost died.
就连义正的姐姐也差点死掉。
I did this
我做了这个
I can never just get over it
我永远无法克服它
No, Uijeong-i watched the whole thing. Is this okay?
不，义正-我目睹了整个过程。 这个可以吗？
But I'm still a police officer
但我仍然是一名警察
You don't have to worry
你不用担心
Now you're mine
现在你是我的了
[Meaningful music]
[有意义的音乐]
(Kichul) Grow up
(基楚尔) 长大了
[Whispering] Oh, what a surprise.
[耳语]哦，真是一个惊喜。
(Democrat) Ah…
（民主党）啊……
What is it, the brother I haven’t seen before?
这是什么啊，我没见过的兄弟？
Oh, I'm the boss' subordinate.
哦，我是老板的下属。
(Minjoo) Ah, yes
（珉珠）啊，是的
Isn't that strange?
这不奇怪吗？
There is no one this handsome around my brother.
我哥哥身边没有一个这么帅的人。
[Minjoo’s light laughter]
[珉祖轻笑]
Ah, humor [laughter]
啊，幽默啊 [笑]
Oh, except for my brother Taeho.
哦，除了我弟弟泰浩。
I've never brought anyone home before.
我以前从来没有带人回家过。
that's interesting
那很有意思
Mr. subordinate
下属先生
(Junmo) Yes
(俊模) 是的
Please be careful not to get stabbed by my brother.
请小心，别被我弟弟刺伤了。
(Minjoo) Although we only see each other occasionally
(珉珠) 虽然只是偶尔见面
I don't want to hear about you on the 9 o'clock news.
我不想在九点新闻中听到你的消息。
then
然后
I'm done
我受够了
I'm going to study before my brother wakes up.
我要在我哥哥醒来之前学习。
[Sound of door opening and closing]
【开门、关门的声音】
[Junmo’s sigh]
[君莫的叹息]
(Chang-sik) You know, Chief, right?
（昌植）队长，你知道吧？
There was a war between the Gangnam Union and the Reconstructionists.
江南联盟和重建派之间爆发了战争。
Don't make it into an incident for now.
暂时不要让它成为事件。
quietly
悄悄
Please bury me quietly.
请安静地埋葬我。
I will make a special request for your cooperation to the chief.
我 会向首长提出一个特别请求，希望你能合作。
ruler
统治者
(Jongryeol) If you don’t send the goods to Japan,
(钟烈) 如果你不把货物寄到日本，
Do we have to digest all 16 kg?
我们 必须消化掉全部16公斤吗？
(Heesung) Hey, look at the Rok Cafe Taeho getting robbed last time.
（熙成）嘿，看看上次韩国咖啡馆太湖被抢劫了。
I'm scared to death to even spray 1kg in Gangnam.
在江南喷一公斤我都害怕死。
As long as Ganttaeng doesn't come out of his stomach
只要Ganttaeng不从肚子里出来
Where and how do you spread 16kg?
在哪里以及如何传播 16 公斤？
How to dispose of things is a problem later.
东西怎么处理是以后的问题了。
Yesterday we all almost died
昨天我们都差点死了
I really need to get an apology from that bastard Kanemoto.
我真的需要得到金本那个混蛋的道歉。
(Hee-seong) That, Yoo Yu-jeong
（熙成）那个，柳有正
I thought they were police because of this incident.
因为这件事我以为他们是警察。
How should I explain it?
我该怎么解释呢？
(Kichul) Tell the truth
(Kichul) 说实话
It's okay, don't worry
没关系，不用担心
(Junmo) Me, boss
(Junmo) Me, boss
Do you mind if I meet the Japanese people in the hotel first?
你介意我先在酒店见见日本人吗？
Didn't you hear me?
你没听到我说话吗？
No, even when you chase away rats, don’t you give them a hole to escape?
不对，就算你赶走老鼠， 你也不给它们留个逃走的地方吗？
(Junmo) So, Japanese bastards, to Oyabung
（纯模）所以，日本混蛋， 去Oyabung
Tell the story well [Meaningful music]
把故事讲好 【有意义的音乐】
Couldn’t someone lighten the mood a bit?
就不能有人 稍微缓解一下气氛吗？
Hey, it's a matter of your boss' pride.
嘿，这是你老板的自尊心问题。
What's important about the atmosphere?
气氛最重要的是什么？
No, does your pride give you food? yes?
不，你的骄傲给你食物吗？是的？
(Junmo) We made a mess like this
（俊模）我们 把事情搞得这么乱
The whole of Gangnam was eaten in one day.
一天之内，整个江南都被吃掉了。
Everyone is watching us from all directions right now .
现在每个人都在从四面八方注视着我们。
In this case , how can you quietly dispose of the item without being noticed ?
在这种情况下，如何才能悄悄地处理掉该物品而不被人发现呢？
Fuck, really, it's only Japan.
妈的，真的，只有日本。
Receive the apology and complete the transaction.
接受道歉并完成交易。
Shouldn't we go in a direction where both are possible ?
难道我们不应该朝两者皆有可能的方向前进吗？
president
总统
This is business
这是生意
(Mingu) Boss Jeong!
（民谷）郑老板！
Boss Jeong is good at fighting!
郑老板很会打架！
Are you there today? huh? [sound of kicking]
今天你在吗？嗯？ [踢腿声]
hey!
嘿！
If you don't come out, we'll attack you!
你再不出来，我们就攻击你！
(Mingu) [Taking a breath] Hey…
(Mingu) [喘口气] 嘿…
What does our boss Jeong like?
我们的郑老板喜欢什么 ？
Even when I get stabbed like this, I hiss
即使我被这样刺伤，我也会发出嘶嘶声
I don't know if they're trying to cover for each other.
不知道他们是不是想互相掩护。
President Jeong, what, did you graduate from the Military Academy?
郑总统，怎么，你是军事学院毕业的吗？
how
如何
Did you pay a lot in condolences to our president Cheon Jin-pyeong ?
您对我们的千镇平总统表示了很多哀悼吗 ？
Errand Center
跑腿中心
I
我
I pulled up the phone call records from our late President Cheon’s office.
我从已故总统千办公室调出了电话记录。
Who was the last person you spoke to?
你最后一次说话的人是谁？
It's you, fuck, Jeong Ki-cheol
是你啊，他妈的，郑基哲
huh? [Kichul laughs]
嗯？ [基楚尔大笑]
what do you think about it?
你怎么看待这件事？
[dark music]
[黑暗音乐]
No, I had to run an errand because I needed to find out something.
不，我 必须去办事，因为我需要找出一些东西。
What's wrong with that?
这有什么问题吗？
Wow, what
哇，什么
Rather than being wrong, it's just fucking scary, huh?
与其说是错了，不如说 是太可怕了，对吧？
President Chun died after I hung up the phone with you , huh?
我挂了你的电话之后，淳总就死了，嗯？
(Mingoo) Your junior drug dealer, Yankee, has disappeared.
(Mingoo) 你的初级 毒贩，洋基，失踪了。
His rival, Assistant Manager Cho, also died.
他的竞争对手曹助理经理也去世了。
Well, at this point
那么，此时
What is happening around President Jeong?
郑总统周围发生了什么？
I wonder if there is a violent crime vending machine or something.
我想知道是否有暴力犯罪自动售货机之类的。
I have reasonable doubt.
我有合理的怀疑。
fuck
他妈的
This is yours too, this
这也是你的，这个
huh?
嗯？
No, fuck it
不，他妈的
[Mingu’s sigh]
[明谷的叹息]
No, but it's so fucking weird again
不，但这又太奇怪了
The cell phone disappeared from President Cheon's belongings ?
手机从千社长的随身物品中消失了？
Did the person who sent the errand take it too?
送差事的人 也接了吗？
or not
或不
Did the Yankees take it?
洋基队拿走了吗？
Find the lighter's owner and ask him.
找到打火机的主人并询问他。
That'll work, huh?
这会起作用，是吗？
(Mingoo) That’ll be fine then
(Mingoo) 那就好了
That'll be fine. [Sound of door closing]
这样就可以了。 [关门声]
What are you talking about, you fucking bastards?
你们这些混蛋在说什么？
What are the sunglasses?
太阳镜有哪些？
[Sound of door opening and closing]
【开门、关门的声音】
Ana, you unlucky bastard, this is it
安娜，你这个倒霉的混蛋，就是这样了
Fuck, I should have been completely killed at that time, but I just
艹，我当时就该彻底被杀了， 可我就是这样
Tsk
茨克
hey
嘿
You leaked this to the police station back then, nigga
你 当时把这个泄露给警察局了，黑鬼
Detective
侦探
I'm thankful for the fire
我感谢火
[Sound of opening the lid]
【打开盖子的声音】
[Sound of the lid closing] It’s not mine.
[盖子关闭的声音] 这不是我的。
Is the timing a little late? [Meaningful music]
时间是不是有点晚了？ [有意义的音乐]
Right?
正确的？
I'm saying it could be yours.
我是说它可能是你的。
It's not
它不是
[Grabbing sound] (Mingu) Hey
[抓取声音] (Mingu) 嘿
Why did your boss chase CEO Cheon, who ordered him to work, to the rooftop?
为什么你的老板要把命令他工作的千首席执行官追到屋顶？
Why did you take President Cheon’s cell phone again?
怎么又拿走了千社长的手机？
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
(Junmo) President Cheon?
（纯模）千社长？
Who are you?
你是谁？
Hey, Seungho Kwon
嘿，权胜浩
I'm not a small bastard like you
我不是像你一样的小混蛋
(Mingu) I want to catch a whale calf
(Mingu) 我想抓鲸鱼宝宝
Jeong Ki-cheol, huh?
郑基哲吧？
Drug dealer Jo's murder charge
毒贩乔被指控谋杀
The Yankees are the ones who can testify to that.
洋基队是可以证明这一点的人。
So bring the fucking Yankees, huh?
所以 带上他妈的洋基队吧？
As long as you catch the Yankees, me and you
只要你抓住洋基队，我和你
[Whispering] You killed CEO Cheon.
[低语]你 杀了千首席执行官。
I won't tell Jeong Ki-cheol.
我不会告诉郑基哲。
No, detective.
不，侦探。
Are you writing novels these days?
你最近在写小说吗？
fun
乐趣
But you have to use words sparingly.
但你必须谨慎使用言语。
Come in
进来
[Mingu’s sigh]
[明谷的叹息]
hey
嘿
But where is that bastard Choi Jeong-bae going these days?
可是 崔正培那个混蛋这几天去哪儿了？
Are you following Jeong Ki-cheol?
你 关注郑基哲吗？
[Elevator arrival sound] [Door opening sound]
[电梯到站声] [开门声]
The plot of the novel is so damn interesting, huh?
小说的情节 很有趣吧？
Right? You bastard
正确的？你这个混蛋
[Sound of door closing]
[关门声]
That fucking guy
那个该死的家伙
[Soft music plays]
[轻柔的音乐响起]
(Regulation) What happened that day
（规定）那天发生了什么
Can you tell me what's going on ?
你能告诉我发生了什么事吗？
(Gi-cheol) Because of the international free city business license
(Gi-cheol) 因为有国际自由城市营业执照
They were competing kids.
他们是竞争的孩子。
I guess they wanted to solve it their own way.
我猜他们想用自己的方式解决这个问题。
I'm really sorry
我真的很抱歉
I really wanted to show my sister a good side.
我真的很想向姐姐展示美好的一面。
Should we continue with that risky business ?
我们应该继续这项危险的业务吗？
I also want to get away from this fist-fighting thing quickly.
我也想快点摆脱这种打架的事情 。
When the International Free City is completed and my name is engraved on it
当国际自由城建成并 刻上我的名字时
Now no one will call me a thug
现在没有人 会称我为暴徒
Then in front of my sister
然后当着姐姐的面
(Kichul) And in front of my sister’s family
(Kichul) 在我姐姐的家人面前
I can stand confidently
我可以自信地站立
[dark music]
[黑暗音乐]
I will never let you get hurt again.
我再也不会让你受到伤害了。
Don't go to places that are too dangerous
不要去太危险的地方
believe
相信
thank you
谢谢
[People talk to each other]
[人们互相交谈]
(Junmo) Are you going to the airport?
(俊模) 你要去机场吗？
I will take care of you
我会照顾你
Uh, I also have something to say quietly.
呃，我也 有话要悄悄说。
I apologize on behalf of our boss.
我代表我们老板向您道歉。
So please let go of your anger
所以请放下你的愤怒
let me ask you a favor
我请你帮个忙
[Oyama clears his throat]
[小山清了清喉咙]
Haven't you seen how we deal with Sung-soo's kids?
你没看到我们是怎么 对待成洙的孩子的吗？
An organization that handles work as reliably and as safely as we do
一个像我们一样可靠、安全地处理工作的组织
We are the only ones in Gangnam right now.
现在江南就只有我们了。
(Junmo) And honestly
（俊模）老实说
Doesn’t the teacher have the power to make the decision?
老师没有 权力做决定吗？
[Meaningful music]
[有意义的音乐]
[Japanese] It’s the right to decide…
[日语] 决定权……
[Korean] We decided to receive double the quantity from China
[韩语] 我们决定从中国接收双倍数量的货物
(Junmo) Well, because of this incident, both Japan and us are affected.
（纯模）嗯，因为这个事件， 日本和我们都受到了影响。
The deficit is not that big.
赤字并没有那么大。
Shouldn’t trade be resumed as soon as possible ?
难道不应该尽快恢复贸易吗？
We will send double the quantity to Japan.
我们 将向日本发送双倍数量。
Well, of course the price is
嗯，当然价格是
equally per kg
每公斤均等
Does Jeong Ki-cheol have the same thoughts as you?
郑基哲也有和你一样的想法吗？
(Mingu) It’s cold.
(明谷) 天气很冷。
What's going on?
这是怎么回事？
(Mingu) No
(民谷) 没有
They say you got away with it
他们说你侥幸逃脱了惩罚
huh?
嗯？
hey you fuck
嘿你他妈的
If something like this happened, you should have contacted me right away.
如果发生这样的事情， 你应该立即联系我。
You made me come this far? uh?
你让我走到这一步了？呃？
uh?
呃？
who is this? Is it regular season?
这是谁？是常规赛吗？
Or is it the little guy next to him named Kwon Seung-ho?
还是他旁边那个叫权承浩的小家伙？
Are you asking something embarrassing like that?
你问这样的问题吗？
(Mingu) Are you embarrassed? uh?
(民谷)你害羞了吗？呃？
What is embarrassing about this?
这有什么好尴尬的呢？
It's embarrassing to be treated like a bloody bastard with no genealogy.
被当作​​一个没有家谱的混蛋对待，真是丢脸。
Hey jockey
嘿骑师
Honestly, you guys are like this.
说实话，你们都是这样的。
Isn’t it okay to fall asleep like this ?
这样睡着不好吗？
I've been looking after you all this time
我一直在照顾你
There shouldn't be a deficit, you bastard.
不应该有赤字， 你这个混蛋。
Yeah, isn't it?
是啊，不是吗？
Our sexual strength has reached its peak?
我们的性强度已经达到顶峰了吗？
Take care of your body, man.
照顾好你的身体，男人。
Don’t search for this because it’s broken, you fucking idiot.
不要搜索这个，因为它已经坏了， 你这个白痴。
What the fuck
搞什么鬼
Not even the old man in the closet, Mr.
就连柜子里的老人也不行，先生。
[Laughing] What is the Reconstructionist, ugh?
[笑] 什么是重建主义者，呃？
No, what are you trying to rebuild?
不，你想重建什么？
Shouldn’t you rebuild your organization ?
难道你不应该重建你的组织吗？
Lucky boy, huh?
幸运的孩子吧？
Oh, fuck, I believe in these things , oh, oh
哦，操，我相信这些东西 ，哦，哦
hey
嘿
Did you recognize what I said then?
你认识我当时说的话吗？
That guy, the Yankees, who treats Gangnam Crystal
那个对待江南水晶的洋基队的家伙
I already looked for it
我已经找过了
I even found out about the guy who was receiving stuff from the Yankees.
我什至发现了那个从洋基队收到东西的人。
who is this? Where are you?
这是谁？你在哪里？
It's the Dodgers
这是道奇队
(Mingu) Dodgers?
（民谷）道奇队？
I'm in the detention center.
我在看守所里。
(Boknam) Seongdong Detention Center
(福南)城东看守所
Oh, you're in the detention center?
哦，你在看守所吗？
(Mingu) Hmm!
（周日）嗯！
Dodgers!
道奇队！
- who are you? - (Mingu) Yes
- 你是谁？ - (民谷) 是的
(Mingu) Yes
(民谷) 是的
huh
呵呵
- (Dodgers) Hwang Min-goo? - (Mingu) Yes
- （道奇队）黄珉九？ - (民谷) 是的
mingu, mingu
敏古, 敏古
(Mingu) Do you want to smoke a cigarette?
（民谷）你想抽烟吗？
hey
嘿
open
打开
Amman, what the fuck is Hwang Min-gu to the detective?
安曼， 黄民九对侦探来说到底是什么？
(Dodgers) I…
（道奇队）我……
Detective, what's going on?
侦探，这是怎么回事？
‘Gangnam Crystal’ bastard
《江南水晶》混蛋
yes?
是的？
(Mingu) Let’s see
(明谷) 来看看
Oh my, if there is 500g of heroin
天哪，如果有 500 克海洛因
Even if you oil this thing, it will last for ten years.
即使你给这个东西上油，它也 能用十年。
Are you screwed?
你完蛋了吗？
Mingu, I just sold it.
明哥，我刚 卖了。
I know, you bastard.
我知道，你这个混蛋。
You know that's why I came, man
你知道这就是我来的原因，伙计
Ah, for simple sales.
啊，为了简单的销售。
(Mingu) The amount I possess is one hundredth.
（民谷）我拥有的数量是百分之一。
If it's 5g
如果是5g的话
That's just a misdemeanor, isn't it?
这只是一种轻罪，不是吗？
Hey Dodgers
嘿道奇队
Junsik
纯植
Shall I do that?
我要这样做吗？
(Dodgers) Yes
（道奇队）是的
Hey [exciting music]
嘿嘿 [激动人心的音乐]
you
你
You can go out with me now
你现在可以和我出去了
Really?
真的吗？
Yes [Mingu’s light smile]
是的 [明谷浅笑]
(Mingu) Hey [throwing sound]
(Mingu) 嘿 [投掷声]
I am
我是
I'm not interested in a piece of shit like you.
我对你这种废物没兴趣。
Do you know what I mean?
你懂我的意思吗？
[Mingu is laughing]
[珉豪笑了]
Let's go out, fuck it.
我们出去吧，他妈的。
- (Mingu) Release me? - (Dodgers) Yes
- (Mingu) 放开我？ - （道奇队）是的
(Mingu) How the fuck can I solve this, you bastard?
（Mingu） 我他妈的该怎么解决这个问题，你这个混蛋？
I have to ask the guard to release me.
我必须请求警卫释放我。
come out
出来
Uh, fuck, my cigarette.
呃，操，我的香烟。
(Junmo) By any chance,
(俊模) 无论如何，
[Sound of door opening and closing] What happened?
[开门和关门的声音] 发生什么事了？
(Kichul) I’ll take you to the hotel.
(Kichul) 我带你去酒店。
[moaning]
[呻吟]
(Detective Ko) Strike
(高侦探) 罢工
[Dodgers cough]
[道奇队咳嗽]
- (Mingu) Hey, Detective Kwon - (Detective Ko) Yes.
- (Mingu) 嘿，权侦探 - (Ko 侦探) 是的。
When did we say we would get together with Kang Dong-seo ?
我们什么时候说过要和姜东瑞在一起的？
next major
下一个专业
[sigh]
[叹]
(Mingu) Can’t you control me? Jegu, huh?
（民谷）你就不能控制我吗？ 杰古吧？
[Mingu’s sound of strength] [Dodger’s groan]
[Mingu 的力量之声] [Dodger 的呻吟]
Mingu hyung, I’m really sorry.
珉哥哥，真的很抱歉。
Why on earth are you doing such a sorry thing?
你到底为什么 要做这么令人遗憾的事？
I'm really really sorry I'm really sorry
我真的真的很抱歉 我真的很抱歉
Why are you doing something so sorry , you fucking bastard?
你为什么要做出如此对不起的事情 ，你这个混蛋？
[Sound of hitting]
[敲击声]
[moaning]
[呻吟]
[Laughing] Strike, strike
[偷笑] 罢工，罢工
[cough]
[咳嗽]
Hey, did I ask you something difficult? huh?
嘿，我 问你什么困难的事了吗？嗯？
Just the Yankees above you
只有你上面的洋基队
(Mingoo) If you just tell me where it is,
（Mingoo） 如果你告诉我它在哪里，
They say they will release you so you can fly freely.
他们说他们会释放你，这样你就可以自由飞翔。
Why the fuck
为什么他妈的
Why don't you understand what I'm saying?
你为什么不明白我在说什么？
You fucking bastard
你他妈的混蛋
Oh, the Yankees and me
哦，洋基队和我
[Crying] The lines are different.
[哭]台词不一样。
[sigh]
[叹]
okay
好的
(Mingoo) Now let’s do some batting practice.
(Mingoo) 现在我们来做一些击球练习吧。
- (Detective Kwon) Yes - (Mingu) Give it to me.
- (权侦探) 是的 - (Mingu) 把它给我。
I am also a blow
我也是打击
[Dodgers’ trembling breathing]
[道奇队颤抖的呼吸]
(Dodgers) Uh, bro, bro, bro, bro
（道奇队）呃，兄弟，兄弟，兄弟，兄弟
No, detective, detective.
不，侦探，侦探。
I don't know anything about the Yankees
我对洋基队一无所知
I really don't know!
我真的不知道！
Oh, and the Yankees, that bastard too
哦，还有洋基队，那个混蛋也是
You're pregnant and need money, huh?
你怀孕了， 需要钱，是吗？
Oh, just increase the number of things.
哦，增加东西的数量就可以了。
They say they take all their customers away and don't do business with them.
他们说他们带走了所有客户并且 不与他们做生意。
What are you talking about? huh?
你在说什么？嗯？
(Mingoo) A bitch?
（明哥）是个婊子？
pregnancy? [Meaningful music]
怀孕？ [有意义的音乐]
(Dodgers) Yes
（道奇队）是的
Oh, that bitch, that bitch is also a druggie.
噢，那个贱人，那个贱人 也是个吸毒者。
Very crazy bitch
非常疯狂的母狗
I guess drug addicts are attracted to each other.
我猜吸毒者 是互相吸引的。
(Mingu) Right?
（民谷）是吗？
(Dodgers) Ah, boy…
（道奇队）啊，孩子……
[response]
[回复]
But you probably don’t know where that girl is anyway.
但你可能根本 不知道那个女孩在哪里。
(Dodgers) Oh, I know.
（道奇队）哦，我知道。
I really know
我真的知道
Really?
真的吗？
Eom Chang
张严
- (Mingu) Hey - (Dodgers) Yes?
- (Mingu) 嘿 - (道奇队) 是吗？
(Mingu) What is Kkalttagu’s name?
(Mingu) Kkalttagu 的名字是什么？
- (Dodgers) Wendy - (Mingu) Shhh! Say quietly, it's a baby
- （道奇队）温迪 - （明古）嘘！悄悄地说，是个宝宝
- (Mingoo) Wendy - (Dodgers) Yes
- (Mingoo) 温迪 - (道奇队) 是的
(Mingu) Hey, go quietly and don’t show off.
(民谷)哎，安静地走吧， 别显摆了。
where are you?
你在哪里？
(Dodgers) W, I think it’s right here.
（道奇队）W，我想就在这里。
that's right
这是正确的
(Mingu) Are you sure, fuck?
(Mingu) 你确定吗，妈的？
- (Mingu) Is that right? - (Dodgers) That’s right.
-（民谷）是这样吗？ - （道奇队）没错。
- (Mingoo) Yankees? - (Dodgers) Yes
-（Mingoo）洋基队？ - （道奇队）是的
(Mingu) Come out
(民谷)出来吧
Come out
出来
[Mingu’s surprised voice] Fuck you, you bastard.
[明谷惊讶的声音] 操你，你这个混蛋。
It's open
已开放
[Switch operation sound]
[开关操作音]
(Mingu) What the fuck, is this a rabbit?
(Mingu) 什么鬼， 这是兔子吗？
[nervous music]
[紧张的音乐]
I threw up
我吐了
You threw up, you fucking bastard.
你吐了，你这个混蛋。
- 토꼈잖아, 개새끼야 - (다저스) 형, 형!
- 토꼈잖아，개새끼야 - (다저스) 형，형！
(Mingu) I told you that if you play like a bully, you’ll fall behind, you fucking bastard.
(Mingu) 我 告诉过你，如果你表现得像个恶霸，你就会落后，你这个混蛋。
Where are you
你在哪
- How do I know it's a rabbit! - (Mingu) Just stay still, fuck, just!
- 我怎么知道这是一只兔子！ - (Mingu) 保持安静，他妈的，只是！
[Japanese] Pathetic guy
[日语] 可怜的家伙
Do I really have to come this far?
我真的必须走到这一步吗？
[dark music]
[黑暗音乐]
Are you asking me to come up here myself?
你要我亲自上来吗 ？
(Kanemoto) [Korean] Shouldn’t you have been there to meet me?
(Kanemoto) [韩语] 你不是应该来接我吗？
I'm a little busy
我有点忙
Are you going to insult me ​​now?
你现在要侮辱我吗？
Is it an insult?
这是侮辱吗？
It's nothing compared to what happened to me.
与发生在我身上的事情相比，这根本不算什么。
[Laughing] Horo bastard
[偷笑]霍罗混蛋
What can I do? I was born an orphan.
我能做些什么？ 我生来就是个孤儿。
[sigh]
[叹]
Don't play with your mouth
别玩嘴
[laugh]
[笑]
[Japanese] Hey, do you know what this guy is saying?
[日语] 嘿，你知道这家伙在 说什么吗？
They say you shouldn’t use your mouth carelessly?
他们说你不应该不小心用嘴？
(Subordinate) You bastard!
（下属）你这个混蛋！
How dare you in front of anyone now!
你现在怎么敢在任何人面前！
(Jongryeol) [Korean] What the fuck are you saying…
(Jongryeol) [韩语] 你他妈的在说什么……
(Junmo) Stay still, stay still
（俊模）别动，别动
[Japanese] Hey!
[日语] 嘿！
stop
停止
[Korean] Put the knife in, Director Seo
[韩] 徐局长，把刀插进去
(Kanemoto) Lastly, I will show generosity.
（金本）最后， 我会表现出慷慨。
Double the quantity
数量加倍
The price is the same
价格是一样的
Those conditions are only after a proper apology.
这些条件 只有在适当的道歉之后才能提出。
bastard
混蛋
I will definitely have to take responsibility for my vain steps .
我一定要为我的徒劳举动承担责任。
[Sound of door opening]
[开门声]
[Sound of door closing]
[关门声]
(Heesung) [Sighing] I thought you were scared, Mr.
（熙成）[叹气] 我以为你很害怕，先生。
What if it goes that hard?
如果事情变得那么艰难怎么办？
If they weren't Japanese, how would they handle that much volume?
如果他们不是日本人， 他们如何处理这么大的音量？
Hey, Gicheol
嘿，吉哲尔
[Sound of door opening]
[开门声]
[Sound of door closing]
[关门声]
fuck
他妈的
[sigh]
[叹]
[Sound of door opening]
[开门声]
(Kanemoto) [Japanese] You idiot
(Kanemoto) [日语] 你这个白痴
[Rhythmic music in the video]
【视频中的节奏音乐】
[Korean] Have you seen this movie?
[韩语] 你看过这部电影吗？
Would you like to watch it together?
你想一起看吗？
sea ​​ryeon
海莲
I need some help, Hae-ryeon.
我需要一些帮助，海莲。
[sigh]
[叹]
(Haeryun) Kanemoto already called his dad.
（海云）金本已经 给他爸爸打电话了。
[popping sound]
[爆裂声]
How about China and Japan do direct trade instead of Korea?
中国和日本不做韩国直接贸易怎么样？
He says he's tired of struggling now .
他说他现在厌倦了挣扎。
[Junmo’s sigh]
[君莫的叹息]
(Junmo) Mr. Haeryeon
(纯模) 海连先生
ah…
啊…
this deal
这笔交易
Not Boss Jeong and Haeryun’s father.
不是郑老板和 海润的父亲。
[Interesting music]
[有趣的音乐]
How about we take some initiative ?
我们采取一些主动行动怎么样？
two of us
我们两个
[light laughter]
[轻笑]
[Switch operation sound]
[开关操作音]
(Oyama) [Japanese] Oyabung
(Oyama) [日语] Oyabung
I'm here to take responsibility for what I said.
我来这里是为了对我所说的话负责。
[Korean] What a great way to treat guests
[韩语] 多么好的待客之道啊
(Haeryun) Why?
(海云)为什么呢？
Search my body again?
又搜查我的身体吗？
(Junmo) Our boss was rude.
(Junmo) 我们的老板 很粗鲁。
I came today to fix that.
我今天来 就是为了解决这个问题。
[Japanese] What is this guy?
【日语】这家伙是什么？
(Ohyama) He’s a smart guy.
（大山）他是个聪明人。
Let's listen to the story.
我们来听听故事吧。
[Korean] Oyabung
[韩语] 欧亚邦
(Junmo) No, if there is someone you don’t want to see in business terms,
（俊模）不，如果有一个你在生意上不想见到的人，
Isn’t it okay if you don’t look at it? yes?
不看不好吗？是的？
Well, first of all
嗯，首先
Let's assume there was no price increase.
我们假设价格没有上涨。
I will take responsibility for sending the items.
我 将负责发送物品。
Why did Miss Lee come?
李小姐怎么来了？
(Haeryun) I also want to talk about business.
(海云)我也想谈生意。
I finished talking about business with my father.
我和父亲谈完了生意。
You haven't even started with me.
你还没有跟我开始。
(Maritime) To send goods from us to Japan
（海运）将货物从我们发送到日本
You must go through Korea
一定要经过韩国
If there is no middle ground, as you just suggested,
如果没有中间立场，就像你刚才建议的那样，
The long distance from China to Japan
中国到日本的距离很远
How would you like to deliver it?
您想如何交付？
Or please suggest an innovative method.
或者请提出一个创新的方法。
I don't think it's something that can be achieved by pushing it recklessly.
我认为这不是一味地推动就能实现的。
My father makes things
我父亲做东西
I deliver it
我交付它
You know, right?
你知道，对吧？
There is no direct transaction
没有直接交易
You want to be my son?
你想成为我的儿子吗？
(Kanemoto) Hey
（金本）嘿
[Japanese] Should I try Yubitsume after a long time ?
[日语] 时隔很长一段时间，我应该尝试一下 Yubitsume 吗？
[nervous music]
[紧张的音乐]
[Korean] What is this?
[韩语] 这是什么？
Because relationships between rich people are not easy to form.
因为有钱人之间的关系 并不容易形成。
(Kanemoto) To have a Yakuza father
（金本） 有一个黑道父亲
Go the Yakuza way
走黑帮之路
No decision, no deal.
没有决定，就没有交易。
[sigh]
[叹]
(Sea Ryun) Definitely
（海莲）绝对
Do we really have to do this?
我们真的必须这样做吗？
[shaking breathing]
[呼吸颤抖]
[Japanese] I think I'm having a hard time alone. Please help me.
[日语] 我觉得我一个人很难过。 请帮我。
[sudden sound]
[突然的声音]
[Sound of wormwood being pulled]
【拔艾草的声音】
[nervous music]
[紧张的音乐]
(Oyama) [Japanese] Nishigawa
(Oyama) [日语] 西川
I considered you a brother.
我把你当兄弟了。
To the person who acknowledges you
致那个认可你的人
the future
未来
How about betting?
投注怎么样？
That means...
这意味着...
It's time for a generational change
是时候进行世代更替了
Where have you seen this before?
你以前在哪里见过这个？
(Ohyama) It’s dangerous
（大山）这很危险
(Kanemoto) Shoot it [gunshot sound]
（金本）射击它 [枪声]
If I were old, I should have disappeared quietly.
如果我老了，我就该悄无声息地消失了。
[Throwing sound]
[投掷声]
(Ohyama) [Korean] He’s like an old dog.
（Ohyama）[韩语] 他就像一只老狗。
[Dark music] [Oyama's sigh]
[黑暗音乐] [大山的叹息]
Now you can do business with me.
现在你可以和我做生意了。
[Haeryun laughs]
[海云笑]
(Haeryun) What is this situation now?
(海云)现在是什么情况？
With President Jeong
与郑总统
The talk is over
谈话结束了
[sigh]
[叹]
(Junmo) No, this now
（俊模）不，现在这个
Have you discussed this with our boss ? yes?
你和我们老板讨论过这个问题吗？是的？
(Ohyama) Now I
（大山）现在我
I'll be President Jeong's new tomodachi.
我将成为郑总统的新知友。
huh?
嗯？
How can I believe it?
我怎么能相信呢？
[laugh]
[笑]
I have to believe it
我必须相信它
Can you help me?
你能帮助我吗？
[Oyama’s light laughter]
[小山轻笑]
[nervous music]
[紧张的音乐]
It's neat
很整洁
You can believe it now, right?
现在你可以相信了，对吧？
Thank you for your hard work
感谢你的努力工作
(Kichul) Now that I’ve sorted out all the troublesome things,
(Kichul) 既然我已经解决了所有麻烦的事情，
Let's start trading again.
让我们重新开始交易吧。
[dark music]
[黑暗音乐]